<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>EAP on Jun Zhang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EAP on Jun Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.151.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:36:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Academic English Writing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/wae194/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:36:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/wae194/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;COURSE DESCRIPTION&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of WAE194 is to provide students with writing experiences designed to improve their academic essay writing skills through the process of prewriting, drafting, and revising. It also strives to build confidence, fluency and grammatical correctness in students’ writing generally, and it serves as preparation for WRT100.  To accomplish these goals, students work on expanding their English competence on the sentence and paragraph levels. Specifically, they work on strategies that promote independence and self-evaluation of their own and others’ writing and produce at least two revised essays.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Academic English Writing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/wae192/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:36:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/eap/wae192/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;COURSE DESCRIPTION&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of WAE 192 is to provide students with writing experiences designed to help them express ideas effectively in sentences, paragraphs, and essays.  Students will develop writing skills with the use of the dictionary, practicing structures of written English, and learning to edit in preparation for advanced editing in WAE 194.  To accomplish these goals, students work on expanding their English competence on the sentence level, expanding their vocabulary through reading and the use of the dictionary, developing strategies that promote independence in writing, and editing personal and peer writing. Grammar proficiency tests are administered throughout the semester. These tests emphasize the use of particular grammatical points in the context of a creative effort on the part of the student.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
